fighting leadership the nifty bank is up
more than 500 points one and a half
percent gain this month uh the nifty
bank has rallied more than about four
percent so significantly outperforming
the benchmark index and it's icsa bank
which is leading from the front in the
last three years icsa bank has rallied
close to about 65 70 percent as compared
to just a 10 rally for hdfc bank and
cotek mahindra bank so icc bank has
clearly been the star in the last three
years and today as well it's
outperforming a fair bit but let's talk
about the insurance data which is out
for the month of june yash is here with
the details yes well rima just look at
the insurance data for the life
insurance sector in the month of june
the industry premium has grown by just
about four percent on a year-on-year
basis in the month of june for the first
quarter it's grown by 40 on a
year-on-year basis private life
insurance is the space where there has
been a strong performance so the june
premium is up 29
first quarter premium of 49 and the june
retail ape has also grown by about 22 on
a year-on-year basis speaking about
individual companies and to start with
the largest one lic the june premium has
has on has seen a contraction of about
five percent that is on a year-on-year
basis for the first quarter the premium
has managed to grow by about 34
and the june retail ape has grown by 21
that is for lic for hdfc life insurance
again the total premium in the month of
june has grown by 11 percent the q1
premium has grown by 27 and the june
retail ape has seen a growth of about
six percent uh icsa prudential life
insurance the june premium uh has seen a
contraction of 15 percent on a
year-on-year basis uh 24 growth for the
first quarter and the june retail ap has
also seen a contraction of about three
percent on a year-on-year basis for max
life insurance the total premium has
seen a growth of about nine percent uh
for first quarter the premium has grown
by 20 percent the retail ap though is
down about two percent now the best uh
is for the last and that is spi life
insurance the june premium has seen a
grown of sixty percent on a year-on-year
basis the first quarter premium growing
by about forty percent the june retail
ap also seeing a strong strong growth of
so sbi life coming out as the strongest
of the lot in the month of june